in business and in your personal life
you're concerned with cybersecurity
because one successful hack could
jeopardize your critical company data or
possibly worse that of your business
partners suppliers and customers and
it's just a matter of time since nearly
60% of recent data breaches have
targeted small businesses but you can be
insured against loss from a cyber
incident cyber insurance can help
protect your business from the financial
impact of a cyber attack a personalized
cyber policy can cover business
interruption losses cyber extortion cost
of IT expert to solve the problem
security and privacy liability
regulatory breach liability crisis
management and other extra expenses
exclusions limits and deductibles apply
get started by contacting us today